themotherlist.com 2019-06-06

# Privacy Policy - The Mother List

The Mother List believes in your privacy. Just as importantly, The Mother List will never rent, share, or sell our subscriber list. We appreciate you joining our site, and we promise not to abuse that trust. We make this promise because we understand just how much you value your privacy. We are moms too. The policy below describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our site and/or register for The Mother List. Please read on carefully.

For more information about the terms and conditions of using this site please see [Terms and Conditions](http://themotherlist.com/terms-conditions/).

By using the website, you signify your assent to our privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of this website following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

#### Your Information

The Mother List doesn’t collect any information except that expressly provided by you. We will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except as required to provide you with the awesome information and insights on The Mother List.

Please be aware that any messages, information or materials you post on The Mother List are not private, are public, and are subject to the terms of this policy. Please do not submit any information to our site that you would like to be kept private or secure. We do not control or regularly review the messages, information or materials posted in the message boards. It is a condition of your use of the message boards and the website that you do not upload to, post, distribute or transmit to or through the website any messages, information or materials which violate or infringe in any way the rights of others, or which are libelous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, threatening, abusive, unlawful or would otherwise violate any law, or encourage such conduct, or which, without our express written consent, contains advertising or any commercial solicitation; post or transmit any material that contains a virus or other harmful component; restrict or inhibit anyone from using and enjoying the message boards.

#### Other Information

In order to make our site better, we may also request other information from you. Just generic stuff — like income level or age, that will help us tailor the site to your needs. We may also share this information with third parties, but only in aggregate, anonymous form. No third party will receive information from us that personally identifies you or anyone else in any way.

#### Usage Information

It is important for us to gather information on how our site is used. All of this information is collected in aggregate form. None of it is personally identifiable. This information will not make it possible for us to corner the market on, say, frozen concentrated orange juice. It’s collected only to help us to, among other things, handle traffic on The Mother List, and to make sure that our service reaches you in the most efficient manner possible.

In the event that we, or any of our affiliates or subsidiaries, are involved in a business transaction such as a merger, an acquisition, a consolidation, a reorganization, a liquidation, or any form of sale of all or a portion of our stock or assets, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to the buyer.

#### How to Unsubscribe

You can unsubscribe from receiving The Mother List emails at any time. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any email and following the instructions.

#### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by Google, our Web advertising partner. View Google’s privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

Occasionally, you’ll get an email marked “Allied Info” in the subject line and in the email header. These emails are not necessarily reflective of the opinions of our editorial staff. They are content paid for by our sponsors (allies), and only reflect the fact that our editorial staff has to put food on the table just like everybody else. Some of this money might also go towards alcohol, but we’re not saying how much.

You can unsubscribe from receiving Allied Info emails. However, if you do so, you will no longer receive The Mother List emails either. You can unsubscribe by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the footer of any email and following the instructions.

#### Cookies

Back in the day, a “cookie” was either something you ate, or a monumentally grating term of endearment. In Internet terminology, cookies are small text files placed on your computer, in order to help websites like ours retrieve information vital to providing the best possible service. Our cookies allow us to recognize you and simplify your user experience. The Mother List will never use cookies to obtain any information from your computer not related to our site.

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

#### Links to Other Sites

The Mother List uses a lot of links. Partly because they allow us to guide you towards valuable products and services. However, we are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

#### Transactions

All transactions placed on The Mother List are processed through a third party vendor that uses Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology to protect your personally identifiable information. SSL encrypts your order information, including your name, address, and payment card number before it is transmitted online.]

Of course, the security of any data transmission over the internet cannot be guaranteed, and any information that you transmit to us is at your own risk.

#### Security

All of the information described above is recorded on embossed sheets of gold leaf locked in steel vaults thousands of feet beneath the earth’s crust, or on our secure server.

#### Modifications

The Mother List may make changes to this policy in the future.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions about this policy, or about the site, please contact us.
